premiumecigarette.com 2018-10-02

# Privacy Policy - Premium Ecigarettes

Premium Ecigarettes created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of our customers. The following discloses our information gathering practices for all of Premium Ecigarettes websites. 

What information do we collect?   
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey.   
Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional.   
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Use of Email Information: Premium Ecigarettes customers and affiliates will receive emails containing information for their orders, such as the receipt of items ordered, price total and personal billing and shipping information.  Customers will receive emails updating their tracking information for their orders too.

Non-personal information:  Like many web sites, we collect and analyze standard log file information and Session ID information to analyze site traffic, improve site performance, and prevent fraud. Session IDs are bits of code on your computer that assist your browser in navigating our site. We do not associate personal information with log file information or cookies, except when needed to prevent fraud.

What do we use your information for?   
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:   
• To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.

How do we protect your information?   
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.   
These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.  
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of online transmission or electronic storage is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.  
We also perform daily website scans backed-up by Scan Alert, to monitor any intrusions from hackers. Scan Alert results are provided 24/7 on our site.

Do we use cookies?   
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information  
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?   
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personal identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance   
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 18 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.

CAN-SPAM Compliance

We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

Online Privacy Policy Only   
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Your Consent   
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.   
This policy was last modified on 10-2010

Privacy Policy Customer Pledge  
We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our privacy policy in line with the the following important privacy laws and initiatives:  
Federal Trade Commision Fair  
California Online Privacy Protection Act  
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act  
Privacy Alliance  
Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act
